<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Luxmarket</string>
    <string name="sony_headphone_desc">"The technology with two noise sensors and two microphones on each ear cup detects ambient noise and sends the data to the HD noise minimization processor QN1. Using a new algorithm, the QN1 then processes and minimizes noise for different acoustic environments in real time. Together with a new Bluetooth Audio SoC "</string>
    <string name="airpods_desc">Up to 2x more Active Noise Cancellation. Transparency mode to hear the world around you. All-new Adaptive Audio intelligently tailors noise control to your environment. Spatial Audio takes immersion to a remarkably personal level. And a single charge delivers 6 hours of battery life.</string>
    <string name="shure_desc">Whether it’s big-time broadcasting, professional podcasts or critical studio recordings, this legendary dynamic microphone delivers smooth, warm vocals every time. The SM7B captures and enhances the finer details of the human voice while blocking out all the distractions. An audio icon. The SM7B is a professional dynamic microphone that operates best with preamps that provide +60dB of gain. Please ensure your audio interface can provide sufficient gain or you may find our SM7dB is a better option with a built-in preamp.</string>
    <string name="sony_camera_desc">The Sony a7 IV Mirrorless Digital Camera is the perfect tool for photographers looking to capture professional-grade images with ease. Boasting an impressive 24.2 megapixel resolution and 5-axis image stabilization, this camera captures stunning photos in almost any lighting situation. Its fast autofocus system keeps objects in focus even when shooting continuously at up to 10 frames per second, while its robust body and weather-sealing make it suitable for shooting in almost any environment With a wide range of customizable features, including an advanced auto-exposure system and an intuitive menu structure, this camera provides users with the control they need to capture amazing images. Whether you’re capturing fast action shots or stunningly detailed landscapes, the Sony a7 IV Mirrorless Digital Camera is sure to impress.</string>
    <string name="redmi_watch_desc">High-resolution and colorful, more details displayedBigger screen-to-body ration, 10% increase from previous model Mi Watch Lite. Better visual and touch control experience.</string>
    <string name="galaxy_bud_desc">"The Samsung Galaxy Buds 2 Pro offer a premium audio experience with features like 24-bit Hi-Fi sound, Active Noise Cancellation (ANC) with three high SNR microphones, and immersive 360-degree audio. They feature an ergonomic design for a comfortable fit, and their IPX7 water resistance rating ensures durability. The earbuds also support features like intelligent voice detection and seamless device switching. With a battery life of up to 8 hours and a compact charging case, the Galaxy Buds 2 Pro are designed for convenience and performance. "</string>
    <string name="podmic_desc">The RØDE PodMic is a USB condenser microphone designed for podcasting, streaming, and voiceover work. Its compact and sleek design, coupled with its exceptional audio quality, makes it a popular choice among content creators. It features USB connectivity, a cardioid polar pattern, zero-latency monitoring, a built-in pop filter, a compact and portable design, and compatibility with various recording software and operating systems. The PodMic is ideal for podcasting, streaming, voiceover work, and home studio recording.</string>
    <string name="google_nest_desc">Google Nest Mini is a compact smart speaker designed to fit seamlessly into your home. Powered by Google Assistant, it allows you to control your smart home devices, play music, set alarms, and answer questions using your voice. With its small size and powerful sound, the Nest Mini is a versatile and convenient addition to any room.</string>
    <string name="gp6_desc">Google Pixel 6 is a flagship smartphone featuring a powerful Google Tensor processor, a dual-camera system with a 50MP main sensor and a 12MP ultrawide lens, and a large, vibrant display. It offers a pure Android experience with regular updates and exclusive Google features like Magic Eraser and Real Tone. With its sleek design, long battery life, and advanced AI capabilities, the Pixel 6 is a top-tier choice for Android enthusiasts.</string>
    <string name="samsungtv_desc">Samsung Crystal UHD DU8000 4K Smart TV (2024) is a 43-inch television that boasts stunning picture quality with Crystal UHD technology. It offers vibrant colors, deep blacks, and sharp details, enhanced by HDR support. The Smart TV platform allows you to access a wide range of streaming apps, games, and content. With features like voice control, screen mirroring, and gaming mode, the DU8000 provides a comprehensive entertainment experience.</string>
    <string name="lenovopc_desc">Lenovo IdeaPad Slim 5i 14IRL8 is a powerful 14-inch laptop equipped with an Intel Core i7-13620H processor and 16GB of RAM. This combination delivers exceptional performance for multitasking, demanding applications, and gaming. The Slim 5i also features a vibrant display, ample storage options, and a comfortable keyboard and touchpad. With its sleek design, long battery life, and a range of connectivity options, it\'s a versatile laptop suitable for both work and play.</string>
</resources>